So, Pheebs, um, you know, I was just
at this bachelorette party, and they had a
cake that was in the shape of a
man's, um...
ding-a-ding-ding.
And, uh, I was wondering, what would you
have thought of that?
Offensive or amusing?
Hmm, I'm not sure.
Monica, what do you think?
Sounds kind of tacky.
Damn it.
Well, I'll just see if they can cancel
it.
And if not, maybe they can just put
eyes on the hoochies and we'll just say
it's some sort of weird elephant.
Hey, hey, you guys, you're not gonna believe
this.
I just got off the phone with my
agent.
Oh, my God!
I'm sorry, too soon.
You go.
I got nominated for my part on Days
of Our Lives!
Joey!
Good for you!
Oh, my God!
I can't believe you're nominated for an Emmy.
No, no.
Oh, soap opera digest award.
Nope.
I'm up for a soapy.
Honey, is that something you're making up?
No, no, no, it's real.
And it has been since 1998.
Okay, they said that they won't cancel the
cake, but I was thinking we could maybe
write NASA on the side and then give
it to Ross.
Hey, wait.
Hi.
I'm up for a soapy.
Oh, my God!
That is like the third most prestigious soap
opera award there is!
Thank you.
Well, I guess now we know who I'm
taking to the awards.
Oh, stop that.
Don't kid about that.
Will all the stars be there?
Many are scheduled to appear.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God, I can't go.
I'm gonna be too nervous.
Okay, I'll go.
No, you're getting married.
This is all I have.
We should celebrate.
Yes, and we will get you a cake
in the shape of a microphone.
With two tennis balls.
So no one told you life was gonna
be this way Your job's a joke, you're
broke, your love life's D.O.A. It's
like you're always stuck in second gear When
it hasn't been your day or week or
month or year But I'll be there for
you Cause you're there for me, too And
it was Ernst Molbrad who first hypothesized that
the velociraptor, when threatened, would expand its collar
and emit a high-pitched noise to frighten
off its predator.
Yes, Mr. Lewis?
What kind of noise?
Just a high-pitched, intimidating noise.
But, like, how?
Well, we don't know for sure.
But in my head, it sounded something like
this.
Of course,
this is just conjecture.
Okay, that's all for today.
Mr. Morris, can I see you for a
moment?
Yes, sir?
Mr. Morris, I need to talk to you
about your midterm exam.
I'm afraid I had to fail you.
Why?
Well, you need 60% to pass.
What'd I get?
Seven.
That's not so good.
No, no, it's not.
What happened there, Ned?
Maybe you can cut me some slack.
I'm sort of in love.
Well, I'm sorry, but that's really not my
problem.
I'm in love with you.
Well, that brings me in the loop a
little.
See, that's why I did so bad on
this test.
I'm having a hard time concentrating.
When you're up there, and you're teaching, your
face gets all serious.
You look so good.
You wear that tight little turtleneck sweater.
Okay.
I, uh, I'm your teacher.
I'm sorry, you're a student, and I like
women, in spite of what may be written
on the backs of some of these chairs.
Oh, my God.
That guy at the counter is totally checking
you out.
Really?
Oh, my God, he's really cute.
Go for it.
Baby, I'm engaged.
I'm just saying, get his number, just in
case.
Look, no, Chandler isn't an accident and can't
perform sexually.
He would want you to take a lover
to satisfy the needs that he has.
He can no longer fulfill.
Hi.
Oh.
Can I just tell you something?
I'm very flattered, but, uh, I'm engaged.
Wow, uh, this is kind of embarrassing.
I was actually coming over to talk to
your friend.
Well, you should be embarrassed.
I thought you knew I was looking at
you.
I did, but that was really fun.
And the winner is Joey Tribbiani.
Oh, wow, I honestly never expected this.
I, uh, I didn't even prepare to speech.
But, uh, I'd like to thank my parents,
who've always been there for me.
I'd also like to thank my friends, Chandler,
Monica, Phoebe, Rachel.
I'm 40.
Jesus.
Look at you with your little maple syrup
award.
Yeah, maybe you don't tell anyone about this.
What?
No, it's not a big deal.
I do that, too, with my shampoo bottle.
Really?
Yeah.
What award are you practicing for?
Grammy.
Best New Artist.
Oh, hey, listen, the Soapy's people called today
and I also get to present an award.
Oh, that's great.
Yeah.
So you'll definitely get on stage, even if
you don't win.
You don't think I'm gonna win?
Of course I do.
But, you know, favorite returning character is a
tough category, Joey.
I mean, you're up against the guy who
survived his own cremation.
I know I might not win, but it's
just...
I've never even been nominated before.
I want it so much.
Well, you know, you'll probably get it.
But you should probably start practicing your gracious
loser face.
You know, like when the cameras are on
you and you want to look disappointed, but
also that your colleague deserved to win, you
know?
So it's sort of like...
Good.
You know?
You practice losing at the Grammys, too?
Oh, no, at the Grammys, I always win.
Ah.
Hey, Mom.
Hey.
This woman only had two bites of her
steak.
Do you want me to wrap it up
for your dog?
Oh, yeah.
What's your dog's name again?
Joey.
Hey.
Oh, how'd your date go with Jake?
Oh, great.
We couldn't keep our eyes off each other
all night.
And then every once in a while, you
know, he'd kind of just lean over and
stroke my hair and then touch my neck.
Okay, stop it.
You're giving me a little tingly.
All I could think of was, you know,
is he gonna kiss me?
Is he gonna kiss me?
And did he?
I'm a lady, Monica.
I don't kiss and tell.
But this hickey speaks for itself.
Okay, okay, I got it, I got it.
I just like him so much that I
just feel like I've had ten drinks today.
And I've only had six.
Well, you know, I haven't had that feeling
since I first started going out with Chandler.
Well, I'm never gonna have that feeling again,
am I?
You sound like a guy.
I know.
A guy would be saying, I'm never gonna
get to sleep with anyone else.
Oh, my God.
I'm never gonna get to sleep with anyone
else.
Are you just realizing this now?
No, maybe, yes.
Oh, my God, I've been so busy planning
the wedding that I forgot about all the
things I'd be giving up.
Man, I'm never gonna have a first kiss
again.
You'll have a last kiss.
Can I ask you something?
You ever had a guy have a crush
on you?
Is that why you wanted to tie my
tie?
There's this kid in my class who said
he's in love with me.
Whoa.
Whoa, what?
Ross has a boyfriend.
I do not have a boyfriend.
There's a guy in one of my classes
who has a crush on me.
Really?
Yeah, I don't know.
I mean, last year Elizabeth, now, now this
kid.
What, what, what is it?
Am I giving out some kind of a
sexy professor vibe?
Not right now.
The point is, my natural charisma has made
him fail his midterm.
Oh, see, now I feel bad for the
kid.
I had a crush on a teacher once,
and it was so hard, you know?
I couldn't concentrate, and I blushed every time
he looked at me.
I mean, come on, you remember what it's
like to be 19 and in love.
Yeah, I guess I can cut him some
slack.
Oh.
How'd you get over that teacher?
I didn't.
I got under him.
Problem solved.
Bye, Phoebe.
Okay, bye.
All right, bye.
Bye.
Bye!
I'll miss you!
I'll miss you, too!
Oh.
Well, we say goodbye at the door so
as not to flaunt our new love.
Oh, Phoebe, it's okay.
It's okay, you don't have to tiptoe around
me.
I've been thinking about it, and, um, you
know what?
I'm okay about not having that new relationship
feeling.
I miss you already!
I miss you, too!
See, that's what I mean.
I mean, that, that's great, but I wouldn't
trade in what I have for that.
I mean, I'm gonna be with Chandler for
the rest of my life, and that's what
makes me happy.
Hey, sweetie, come here, let's go sit down.
Hey, Phoebe and I were just talking about
how our relationship is deep and meaningful.
It really is, don't you think?
Oh, totally.
Pull my finger.
Hey, everybody, we're back in 30.
Where have you been?
They're about to give out my award.
Oh, well, I was in the bathroom, and
Susan Ritchie came out of a stall, and
she had toilet paper on her shoe, so
I took it.
This is, this is, this is my category.
Oh, my God.
Did you have the speech?
Yeah, I got the speech.
Did you get your gracious loser face?
Yep.
Oh.
Now, Joey, remember, if you win, you have
to hug me.
Hug me.
Can I squeeze your ass?
On TV?
Yeah.
But these four exceptional actors have proven that
this is not always the case.
In the category of favorite returning male character,
the nominees are John Wheeler from General Hospital,
Gavin Graham from The Young and the Restless,
Duncan Harrington from Passions, and Joey Tribbiani from
Days of Our Lives.
And the Sophie goes to Gavin Graham from
The Young and the Restless.
Presenting the award for favorite supporting actress is
Joey Tribbiani from Days of Our Lives.
Any one of the brilliant actors who is
nominated for this award tonight deserves to take
it home.
Unfortunately, only one can.
The nominees for favorite supporting actress are from
Passions, Aaron Goff, from One Life to Live,
Mary Lauren Bishop, from All My Children, Sarah
Grinnell, and from Days of Our Lives, Jessica
Ashley.
And the winner is Jessica Ashley from Days
of Our Lives.
Unfortunately, Jessica couldn't be with us tonight, so
I'll be accepting this award on her behalf.
And I'm sure that Jessica would like to
thank my parents, who always believed in me.
She'd also like to thank my friends, Chandler,
Monica, Ross, Phoebe, and Rachel, who's sitting right
there.
Why did we have to rush out of
there so fast?
It was this close to getting Luca DeLorean
to sign Susan Lucci's toilet paper.
But we had to get out of there
because look what I won!
Oh my God, you stole her award.
No, no, no.
I'm accepting it on her behalf.
Joey, I don't think you know what behalf
means.
Sure I do.
It's a verb.
As in, I be halfening.
You have got to take this back.
Why?
I should have won one.
And I really wanted it.
She didn't even care enough to come to
the thing.
It could also be a Grammy.
No, Joey.
Come on, Rach.
No one saw me take it.
There was a whole table full of them.
Do you really want an award that you
didn't win?
No, I want an award I did win.
But nobody's giving me any of those.
Plus, okay, if I put it up there,
right?
When people come over, they'll see it and
they'll think I won it.
Joey, it says Best Supporting Actress.
I could scratch that right off.
Joey, no, this is wrong.
You have to take it back, okay?
You don't want to win an award this
way.
You're very talented.
And someday you're going to win one of
these for real and that one is going
to mean something.
All right.
All right, thank you.
I'll take it back tomorrow.
Thank you.
If I can't have it, you can't have
it.
Professor Geller?
Yes, Mr. Lewis, how can I help you?
I know I didn't do you well on
my midterms and stuff, but I was kind
of hoping you could change my grade.
Why exactly would I do that?
Because I'm in love with you.
What?
Yeah, I'm all in love with you and
stuff.
So could you change my grade?
No!
Why not?
You changed Ned's grade.
Well, that's different, okay?
Because he was actually in love with me.
No, he's not.
He's totally yanking your chain.
He's done this with three other teachers.
What?
He's got a girlfriend.
I can't believe someone would do that for
a grade.
I know.
It's awful.
I love you.
All right.
What?
It's true.
Okay, okay.
Oh, you love me?
You love me?
You love me so much, come over here
and give me a kiss.
You got an 80!
You didn't even fail!
Have some self-respect!
Have you seen Chandler?
No.
Why?
Because I just keep thinking about all these
things that I'm not gonna have, and it's
freaking me out.
I don't know what to do about it.
Okay, don't sweat it.
Chandler is nowhere around, so go ahead, get
it out of your system.
That guy's cute.
Phoebe, come on, I'm serious.
I just gotta talk to him about all
this.
No, that is the last thing you wanna
do.
Why?
Because you're marrying him.
You gotta help me out here, Phoebs.
All right, I've never been engaged, and I've
never really been married.
Look, I can only tell you what my
mother told me.
Whenever you have doubts or fears or anxieties
about a relationship, do not communicate them to
your husband.
So I'm not supposed to share my doubts
and fears with the guy I'm gonna spend
the rest of my life with?
That is correct!
Yes, you're supposed to take all that stuff
and put it in a little box in
your mind and then lock it up tight.
Your mother told you this?
Yes.
The woman that got married a bunch of
times and killed herself when you were 13?
Oh, my God, you're right.
All right, go.
Go tell Chandler.
Hurry, before it's too late!
Wait, no!
Does this also mean that putting out doesn't
get you left?
I can't believe I'm gonna meet Jessica Ashley!
Wait, wait, wait.
Please, be cool, okay?
I work with this woman.
Okay, I'm totally cool.
Come in.
Hey, Jessica.
Hey, Jess.
This is my friend Rachel.
Hi.
What's up?
Listen, here's your selfie.
I accepted it for you.
Oh, my God, I won?
Do you have any idea what this means?
That's it?
You're not gonna...
You're not gonna put it on your shelf
or anything?
No, I try to save that for real
awards.
Now, if you'll excuse me.
Take it back?
Absolutely.
Yeah, you do.
Honey?
As we get closer to their wedding, is
there anything that you'd like to talk about
or share?
Okay.
Well, I think the centerpieces are too big.
You're wrong.
The centerpieces are fine.
Do you ever get scared at all?
Kind of.
They're really big.
Doesn't it just ever freak you out that...
that you're never gonna be with anybody new
again?
What?
Just...
I love you so much.
It's...
It's just sometimes it bothers me that I'm
never gonna have that feeling.
You know, when you meet someone for the
first time and it's new and exciting?
You know that rush?
No.
No, see, when I first meet somebody, it's,
uh...
it's mostly panic, anxiety, and a great deal
of sweating.
Okay, but...
All right, you're a guy.
Does it not freak you out that you're
never gonna sleep with anybody else?
Sleeping with somebody new...
Anxiety, panic, and, I'm afraid, even more sweating.
Even with me?
I was dangerously dehydrated during the first six
months of our relationship.
Look, for me, the rush is knowing that
we are gonna be together for the rest
of our lives.
Really?
Well, yeah.
But now that I know that you're having
these thoughts, we're back to panic, anxiety, and,
uh, I'm definitely gonna need some kind of
sports drink.
Oh, sweetie, you don't have to worry.
No.
Besides, you know what?
I'm gonna have a lot of new things
with you.
The first time we buy a house, our
first kid, our first grandkid.
Water, water, water.
Uh, Mr. Morse, can I speak to you
for a moment?
That was a great lecture today.
Did you get a little haircut?
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, yeah.
Do you like it?
Do you love it?
I just want you to know that I'm
changing your grade back.
What?
Why?
Because I know what you're trying to pull
here, okay?
It's not gonna work.
I'm not trying to pull anything.
Look, I love you, dude.
You know what?
I'm not even gonna talk about this, okay?
This little thing is over.
I know you have a girlfriend, okay?
Yeah, and I know about the other professors.
How do you think that makes me feel,
Ned?
You used me.
You don't love me, and you never did.
Ah, Professor Winston, Professor Fredrickson.
I'll be right with you.
Don't make this worse, and I'll give you
a C.
Shall we?
Rach, I'll be out in a second.
It's just so unexpected.
I...
I'll tell you, it's just such an honor
to just be nominated for a Nobel Prize.
And, you know, to win one for a
massage.
Especially after having just won a Tony Award
for Best Actress in...
Honey, we have to go.
Our reservations are at 8.
In reservations at 8.
By Neil Simon.
Thank you.
Thank you, Neil.
Thank you for the words.
Okay, honey, you can finish this later.
We're gonna be late.
We gotta go.
Please don't play the music.
I just have one more thing.
Live from New York, it's Saturday night!